[
  {
    "question":"Command for creating the project structure in Cucumber?",
    "correctAnswer":4,
    "options":["rspec --start","gherkin --init","cucumber --start","cucumber --init","ruby --start"]
  },
  {
    "question":"What is the correct way to write a JavaScript array?",
    "correctAnswer":3,
    "options":["var colors = 'red', 'green', 'blue'","var colors = (1:'red', 2:'green', 3:'blue')","var colors = ['red', 'green', 'blue']","var colors = [1:'red', 2:'green', 3:'blue']","var colors = {'red', 2:'green', 3:'blue'}"]
  },
  {
    "question":"In which file can we create our scripts in Cypress?",
    "correctAnswer":3,
    "options":["env","file","package","node","description"]
  },
  {
    "question":"What is the name of the Ruby package manager?",
    "correctAnswer":2,
    "options":["npm","bundler","yarn","rubler","ant"]
  },
  {
    "question":"How does a FOR loop start in Js?",
    "correctAnswer":2,
    "options":["for (i = 0; i <= 5)","for (i = 0; i <= 5; i++)","for i = 1 to 5","for (i <= 5) then i++","i++ for(i = 0; i <= 5)"]
  },
  {
    "question":"Has a parameter that is a callback function in Cypress",
    "correctAnswer":1,
    "options":["beforeEach","afterAll","enabled","describeEach","embedAll"]
  },
  {
    "question":"Command to install project dependencies in Ruby?",
    "correctAnswer":5,
    "options":["rspec install","bundle start","ruby start","npm init","bundle install"]
  },
  {
    "question":"How to write an IF statement in JavaScript?",
    "correctAnswer":1,
    "options":["if (i == 5)","if i = 5 then","if i == 5 then","if i = 5 :","case i = 5 then"]
  },
  {
    "question":"Used to create a test case in Cypress",
    "correctAnswer":5,
    "options":["at","go","on","start","it"]
  },
  {
    "question":"Complete with the correct term. cucumber ____ @ scenario1, @ scenario2, @ scenario3",
    "correctAnswer":2,
    "options":["-keys","--tags","-scene","--keys","-tags"]
  },
  {
    "question":"How do you create a function in JavaScript?",
    "correctAnswer":3,
    "options":["function:myFunction()","function = myFunction()","function myFunction()","function = new myFunction()","function = new 'myFunction()'"]
  },
  {
    "question":"Retrieves an element on the screen that contains a defined character string in Cypress",
    "correctAnswer":4,
    "options":["hold","have","stifle","contains","get"]
  },
  {
    "question":"Executed before or after starting the execution of a scenario in Cucumber",
    "correctAnswer":3,
    "options":["setup","precode","hooks","kit","master"]
  },
  {
    "question":"How do you write 'Hello World' in an alert box in Js?",
    "correctAnswer":2,
    "options":["msg('Hello World');","alert('Hello World');","alertBox('Hello World');","print('Hello World');","show('Hello World');"]
  },
  {
    "question":"Are scripts executed before the request is sent in Postman",
    "correctAnswer":4,
    "options":["before-script","before-all","previous-scripts","pre-request","fore-all"]
  },
  {
    "question":"In Cucumber are types of reports generated during execution",
    "correctAnswer":1,
    "options":["pretty/progress","report/resume","beauty/resume","progress/report","dynamic/resume"]
  },
  {
    "question":"Used to check if the text exists in the element in Capybara",
    "correctAnswer":3,
    "options":["it_content?","fill_in","has_content?","npm_in","fill_content?"]
  },
  {
    "question":"Is a type of markup language",
    "correctAnswer":2,
    "options":["json","xml","ajax","asp","prototype"]
  },
  {
    "question":"Command to generate report in Capybara",
    "correctAnswer":2,
    "options":["--resume","--out report","--ruby text","--out init","--bundle"]
  },
  {
    "question":"It is associated with the page object",
    "correctAnswer":3,
    "options":["grouping","blend","encapsulation","arrangement","binding"]
  },
  {
    "question":"What file does the gem install command reference in Capybara?",
    "correctAnswer":5,
    "options":["rspec","helper","index","hooks","gemfile"]
  },
  {
    "question":"Known as Server authorization issued to the client.",
    "correctAnswer":2,
    "options":["auth","bearer","key","staff","holder"]
  },
  {
    "question":"Command to access a url in Capybara",
    "correctAnswer":2,
    "options":["go_to","visit","browser","url_to","flow"]
  },
  {
    "question":"Where do we group our requests in Postman?",
    "correctAnswer":4,
    "options":["group","joint","set","collection","compilation"]
  },
  {
    "question":"Designed in RFC 4627 standard",
    "correctAnswer":4,
    "options":["ajax","xml","ecma","json","w3c"]
  }
]
